你们在干嘛？莫妮卡逼我们看《老黄狗》（又译《父亲离家时》）
-What you guys doing? -Monica's making us watch Old Yeller.
那你们在伤心什么？ 这是一部快乐的电影啊
Why are you guys upset? It's Old Yeller. It's a happy movie.
什么？ 你在胡扯什么？
-What? -What are you talking about?
少来了，快乐家庭养了一只狗
Come on. Happy family gets a dog.
荒野之乐
Frontier fun!
对呀，但是结局呢？
Pheebs,what about the end?
是老黄救全家人于狼口之中 大家皆大欢喜
When Yeller saves the family and everyone's happy?
那不是结局
That's not the end.
才是呢，我妈会在那个时候 关掉电视说已结束了
That's when my mother would shut off the TV and say,"The end."
那它生狂犬病的情节呢？
What about when he has rabies?
它没有生狂犬病 它生了小宝宝
He doesn't have rabies. He has babies.
我妈说的
That's what my mom said.
菲比，我猜你妈 不想你看接下来的剧情
I don't think she'd want you to see what's about to happen.
为什么？接下来怎么样？
Why? What's about to happen?
这部份我从没看过
I've never seen this part.
崔维，你拿枪干什么？
Hey,Travis,what you doing with that gun?
不…
Oh,no.
崔维，把枪放下来
No,no,Travis,put down the gun.
不要…它是你的伙伴 是你的老黄
No,no,he's your buddy. He's your Yeller.
不…剧终…
No! The end! The end!
这算什么病态的狗电影？
Okay,what kind of a sick doggy snuff film is this?
六人行 第2季 第20集 老黄狗之死
The One Where Old Yeller Dies
你们吃过了吗？我跟理查 刚吃过，我们还有剩菜
Have you guys eaten? Richard and l just finished,and we've got leftovers.
鸡肉跟马铃薯
Chicken and potatoes.
我穿什么？
What am I wearing?
事实上，除了塑胶手套之外什么都没穿
Actually,nothing but rubber gloves.
有一天你会真的一丝不挂 而我们却不会过来了
One of these times,you'll really be naked and we won't come over.
这倒是给我上了一课
That'd teach me a lesson.
我还剩一条腿，三块胸跟一根翅膀
I got a leg,three breasts and a wing.
那你怎么找得到合适的衣服穿？
How do you find clothes that fit?
莫妮卡，我们有问题
Hey,Monica? We got a question.
好吧，再说一遍，对，我在健身房浴室会看到别的女人
All right,yes,I see other women in the shower at the gym.
不，我没兴趣看
And no,I don't look.
不，不是那个
No,not that one.
我们在想今晚带谁去看尼克队赛球，我们多了一张票
We're figuring out who to bring to the Nicks game.
对，罗斯不能去，所以或者是我朋友艾瑞克，他有口臭
Ross can't go,so it's between my friend Eric Prower,who has breath issues...
…或是丹，他爱戳人 “你看到了吗？”
...and Dan,with the poking. "Did you see that play?"
“还要啤酒吗？” “那是史派克李吗？”
"You want more beer? Is that Spike Lee?"
为什么不问理查？
Why don't you ask Richard?
理查，如果你有多一张 尼克队球赛的票…
Richard,if you had an extra ticket to the Nicks game...
…而你必须从有口臭…
...and you had to choose between a friend who smelled...
…跟会戳人的朋友当中选 你会选谁？
...and one who bruises you,who would you pick?
对一个大尼克迷来说…
Being a huge Nicks fan myself...
…我想你们应该选一个 大尼克迷
... I think you should take someone who's a huge Nicks fan.
那就艾瑞克好了
That's Eric.
乐意效劳，不客气
Glad to be of help. Matches.
我是说 你们为什么不请理查去？
I meant,why don't you take Richard to the game?
怎么样？
What?
我不知道 拜托
-I don't know. -Come on!
他从来不会乱指乱戳 口气永远芳香自然
He keeps his fingers to himself,and he's always minty fresh.
理查他这个人真的很好啦 只是我们跟他不是很熟
Richard's really nice. We just don't know him really well.
加上他又老…
Plus,he's old
…一点儿，对某些人来说
er than some people.
但他比某些建筑要年轻一点
But younger than some buildings.
他老一点又怎么样？
So what,he's a little older. Big deal.
他对我而言是很重要的
He's important to me.
你们问他的话 他或许会开捷豹去哦
If you ask him,he might take you in his Jag.
我们要怎么说…
How do we say yes...
…才不会听起来像 为了要搭他的酷车才邀请他去
...and make it seem like it's not just to ride in the cool car?
这有点棘手
Okay,this could be tough.
他如果开捷豹车来 我们才会带他去
We'll bring him,but only if he takes the Jaguar.
你几乎办到了
You almost had it.
不…你没问题…
No,no,you're fine. You're fine.
亲爱的
Hi,honey.
你们一定不会相信 发生了什么事
You are not gonna believe what happened!
我们坐在那边地板上玩 他抓住了桌子…
We were playing on the floor,and he grabs the table...
…把自己拉起来了
...and he pulls himself up!
他把自己拉起来了
He pulled himself up!
站立的人
Standing man!
很遗憾你们错过，但我录下来了，你们要看的话…
I'm sorry you missed it,but I did tape it if you wanna see it.
我们知道，他上个礼拜就会了
We know. He already did it last week.
你可以看我们的带子
You can watch our tape if you want.
我真不敢相信 我错过每个第一次了
See,I don't believe this. I missed the first time of everything.
我错过他第一次翻身 他第一次爬
The first time he rolled over,the first time he crawled.
我还错过了什么？ 他说话了吗？会开车了吗？
What else? Has he spoken? Is he driving?
他有偏好的甜酒吗？
Does he have a favorite liqueur?
他好像也快要会说话了
He is getting closer on the talking thing.
他还不会说妈妈 可是有一次他说“也门”
He can't quite say "mama" yet,but once he said "Yemen."
我受不了老是错过
See,I don't know. I'm so sick of missing stuff.
我不要只照顾他一天而已 我要他一整个周末
I want him for more than a day. I want him for a whole weekend.
听着，我觉得…
Listen. I feel
没问题
That would be great.
真的？我正准备要大发议论
Really? I had a whole speech prepared.
是的，那会很好玩的
Oh,shoot,that would've been fun.
你们看到了吗？
Did you just see that?
他刚刚挥手…
Did you see? He just waved! He just waved!
他从来没有挥过手
He's never waved before!
他挥过？好极了
Yes,he has. Very good.
菲比，那是什么？
What you got there?
“爱情故事”“布莱恩之歌” 还有“母女情深”
Love Story,Brian's Song and Terms of Endearment.
现在只缺“战火屠城” 跟一些鳄梨色拉酱你就可以狂欢了
All you need now is The Killing Fields and guacamole,and you got a party!
对呀，我跟我外婆讲了 那个“老黄狗”那件事…
I talked to my grandma about the Old Yeller incident...
…她说我妈总是不让我们看 那种悲伤电影的结局…
...and she said my mom used to not show us the ends of sad movies...
…好让我们不用痛苦伤心
...to shield us from the pain and sadness.
你们知道的，是在她自杀之前
You know,before she killed herself.
他人呢？理查呢？ 你们甩了他吗？
Where's Richard? Did you ditch him?
对，在抢了他的午餐钱还有拉了他内裤（国外小孩的恶作剧）之后
After we stole his lunch money and gave him a wedgie.
你这人怎么搞的？他在停车
What's the matter? He's parking the car.
那你们玩得开心吗？ 你的男朋友真的好酷
-Did you guys have fun? -Your boyfriend is so cool.
对，他让我们开他的车 乔伊12条街，我15条街
He let us drive his Jaguar. Joey for 12 blocks. Me for 15.
他一定最喜欢你
He must like you best.
还有他给那个 帮我们带位的人小费那件事
What about when he tipped the guy who showed us to our seats?
他连多少都没看，就像这样
You never even saw the money.
钱德，谢谢你帮我们带位 不用客气
Hey,Chandler,thanks for showing us to our seats.
乔伊，谢谢你帮我停车
You're welcome. Hey,Joey,thanks for parking the car.
没问题
No problem.
钱德… 我想她们懂了
-Hey,Chandler -I think they get it.
他来了
There's the man!
你越来越行了
Hey,you're getting better.
我要留着这个
I'm gonna keep this.
他留下我的钱
He kept my dollar.
第一个没有班的周末 你们两个要做什么？
Your first weekend without Ben. What are you doing?
我们要去威廉斯堡玩
We're going to colonial Williamsburg.
对，我大学一个女同学 刚成为那里第一个女铁匠
A woman I went to college with is the first female blacksmith there.
威廉斯堡那边是有点落伍了
They're a little behind the times in colonial Williamsburg.
好吧 我们最好在掉眼泪之前走了
Look,I better go before Mommy starts weeping.
我们爱你 再见，妈咪
-We love you. -Bye,Mommy.
好好玩
Have a good time.
看
Look.
乔伊 你知道我们看得到你吗？
Joey,do you know we can see you from here?
为什么理查抽起这个 比我酷那么多？
How come Richard looks cooler with one of these?
首先，你或许要先点燃 还有放下那支锅铲
You may wanna light it and lose the spatula.
你想模仿理查，我觉得很可爱
It's cute,you trying to be more like Richard.
也不是要像他
Not like him,per se.
只是不要不像他
Just not unlike him.
看，是以前 叫钱德的那个艺术家
It's the artist formerly known as Chandler.
我不过是想试试看
I'm just trying something here,you know?
乔伊，你为什么不留胡子？
Why didn't you grow a mustache?
我们丢铜板
We flipped for it.
我丢到抽雪茄，他丢到留胡子
I got the cigar,he got the mustache.
我想我们都留胡子的话会有点像呆子
If we both grew them,we'd look like dorks.
是呀，你们真的躲过那一劫了
You really sidestepped that land mine.
我们得走了 我答应理查在楼下见
I promised Richard we'd meet him downstairs.
你们要见理查？
You're meeting Richard?
对，我们要去看曲棍球赛 对，他没告诉你吗？
-Ranger game. -Didn't he tell you?
他告诉我他跟伙伴出去 我只是不知道伙伴是你们
He said he was going out with the guys. I didn't know that was you.
你听到了吗？
You hear that?
我们是伙伴
We're the guys!
钱德留那胡子 像不像西维亚姑妈？
With that mustache,he reminds me of Aunt Sylvia.
谢谢
Thank you!
中央公园
我们来拜访
Hi. We're visiting.
是小班跟他爹爹
It's Ben and his dada.
你会说“爹爹”吗？
Can you say "dada"?
我会告诉你的妈咪们你说了，你试试啊
I'm telling your mommies you said it,so you might as well.
运气不好？
No luck,huh?
不好，不久以前 他发了一个“二”的音
A while ago,I got a "se" out of him...
我想那也可以勉强说 是二褓姆的意思…
...which I thought might turn into "se-condary caregiver," but....
帮我抱一下，好吗？ 我得把这个拿下来
Would you hold him for a sec? I gotta take this off.
好的
Sure. Okay.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
我在抱班啊
I'm holding Ben.
对，他是个婴儿，不是炸弹
He's a baby,not a bomb.
你可以像抱足球那样抱他
Hold him like you'd hold a football.
我就是这样抱足球的
This is how I would hold a football.
来…这样
Here. Here. There we go.
对不起，我不太会带孩子 我是说，我没接触过他们
Sorry,I'm not very good with babies. I haven't been around them.
从我长大以后啦
I mean,you know,since I was one.
没关系，没什么大不了的 真的？
-It's all right. No big deal. -Really?
我相信如果他是我们的宝宝 会让你感觉不一样
I'm sure you'll feel different when it's our baby.
什么？ 什么？
-What? -What?
你想那一类的事？
You think about stuff like that?
对，我是说…
Yeah. I mean....
事实上，我想我们会有 有两个宝宝
Actually,I kind of think that we'll have two babies.
两个宝宝？
Two babies?
对，一男一女
You know,a boy and a girl.
我希望先是女的，所以小班 不会觉得有太大的竞争
Hopefully,the girl will come first,so Ben won't feel competitive.
那接下来呢？
Then what's gonna happen?
我们不希望孩子在城市里长大 所以我们或许会搬到斯卡斯代尔镇
We won't wanna raise kids in the city,so we'll move to Scarsdale.
我们会住得离我们的父母够远 所以不用常常看到他们…
We'll be far enough from our parents so we don't have to see them...
…但又不会太远 所以随时可以请他们来带小孩
... but close enough that they can baby-sit.
没错，我知道那里的税是比拿骚郡要高一点…
And yes,I know the taxes are a little higher than Nassau County...
…但学校制度据说非常非常棒
... but the school system's great.
太棒了…
Wow,that's great! Great!
你知道吗？
Okay,wow! You know what?
我休息完了
I'm off my break now.
所以你拿着
Here. You take this.
我要去帮这些好人倒咖啡了
I'm gonna go pour these very nice people some coffee.
你瞧瞧，我没有咖啡壶
Look at that. I don't have a pot.
或许我家里有一个
I don't have a pot. Maybe I've got one at home.
或是斯卡斯代尔，那是门吗？
Or in Scarsdale. Hey,is that a door?
菲比，怎么了？
Hey,Pheebs. What's happening?
谋杀，癌症 足球队在安地斯山脉吃来吃去
Murder,cancer,soccer teams eating each other in the Andes.
-其实我只是随口打个招呼而已 -我只是在发泄情绪
-I was really just making small talk.-Well, I was just venting.
你看了电影了？
So you watched the movies?
这个世界到底怎么了？
What is happening to the world?
我是说，因为ET走了（《ET外星人》）…
I mean.... No,no,because E.T. Ieaves...
洛基输了（史泰龙的《洛基》），夏洛特死了（《夏洛特的网》）
...and Rocky loses. Charlotte dies.
哪个夏洛特？
Charlotte who?
蜘蛛网，那只蜘蛛
With the web. The spider.
她死了，她生了宝宝后就死了
She dies. She has babies and dies.
那就像…“欢迎从医院回来”砰！
It's like,"Welcome home from the hospital." Thud!
想不想好受一点？
You wanna feel better?
来，看这个
Here. Watch this.
是“美好人生”（又译《风云人物》）这个我听说过
It's a Wonderful Life. I've heard of this.
所以没问题，片名说明了一切
So you can't lose. It's there in the title.
包你美妙得不得了
Wonderfulness is baked right in.
拜托，我已经被《扬基的骄傲》给骗了 （讲述球员卢格里克生病去世的故事）
I fell for that with Pride of the Yankees.
我以为是关于扬基队的骄傲的故事
I thought I'd see a film about Yankee pride.
然后… 那个家伙得了卢格里克症
And boom! The guy gets Lou Gehrig's disease.
那个家伙就叫卢格里克 你没预感吗？
The guy was Lou Gehrig. Didn't you kind of see it coming?
你看就是了，我保证能让你恢复对人类的信心
Watch that. It'll restore all your faith in humanity.
大个儿，球赛时间到了
Hey,big guy. Game time.
好，马上来 有球赛？
-Hey! Be right there! -There's a game?
对，我刚从店里 拿了棍子玩具回来
I just got my Pik-Up Stiks back from the shop.
带着你的铁胆来
Bring your nerves of steel.
是篮球决赛
It's the basketball playoffs.
亲爱的，你这样我很感激 但是你不用为了我跟他们混
I appreciate this,but you don't have to hang out with them for me.
反正他们两个可以做伴
They have each other.
不，亲爱的，别担心
Oh,no,honey. I mean,don't worry.
我很喜欢跟他们混，很好玩 他们跟我别的朋友不同
I like hanging out with them. They're different than my other friends.
他们不会一见面就说 “你知道谁铲雪时死了吗？”
They don't start sentences with "You know who just died shoveling snow?"
好吧，那就去吧
All right,that's great. Then just go.
加油，尼克队
Go Nicks!
是大学篮球决赛
It's the college playoffs.
加油，瓦萨大学 他们没在这个联赛里
-Then,go Vassar! -They're not in it.
那加油吧
Okay,then just go.
我为什么要那么在意呢？
Why does this bother me so much?
我并不想当那种要男友24小时都在一起的人
I'm not one of those people who wants to spend 24 hours a day together.
对呀
Sure.
只是他空闲的时间不多 我不知道，我到底该怎么办？
He just doesn't have much free time. What do I do?
有关系吗？你始终都会死 或离婚，或枪杀你的宠物
Does it matter? You'll just die or divorce or blow your pet's head off.
我也是
Me too!
瑞秋，我有个问题 理查又跟他们做计划了…
Rachel,I got a question. Richard made plans again with the guys
对，罗斯刚计划了整个世纪
Ross made plans for the century.
我想我要回房去看时尚杂志了 或许会读到什么有用的
I'm gonna go read Cosmo. Maybe there's something helpful in it.
不然至少可以学会 怎样用圣诞树剩下的蜡烛除毛
If not,I can learn how to do a bikini wax with leftover Christmas candles.
你刚刚是怎么回事？
What happened back there?
不知道，你告诉我吧
I don't know. You tell me.
我刚刚还像抱足球一样抱着班 接下来我就有两个孩子…
One minute I'm holding Ben,then I've got two kids...
…住在斯卡斯代尔，抱怨着税太高
... I'm living in Scarsdale complaining about taxes!
那抱歉，我就是爱想些事情
Well,I'm sorry. I think about stuff.
我是说，工作的时候 一边弄骨头就会一边乱想嘛
You're at work,you're assembling bones,your mind wanders.
你计划了我们往后二十年生活 我们才在一起六周
You've planned out the next 20 years. We've dated for six weeks!
你从不想未来的事吗？
You never think about our future?
想，但我想的是 我们明晚住谁那边好…
I think about whose apartment we'll sleep at tomorrow...
…下个礼拜六晚上 我们去哪里吃晚饭
...and where we'll have dinner next Saturday!
我不会去想 我们的孩子会叫什么名字
I do not think about our children's names!
你知道我们的孩子会叫什么名字对吧？
You know what our children's names will be?
不…我…我是说我看到一本书 里头有个女孩叫艾蜜莉
No,I mean,you know. I read a book,and there was a girl named Emily.
我觉得…我觉得还不错
And I thought that might be good.
哪一本书？
What book?
“儿童命名大全”
The Big Book of Children's Names.
你听着
Okay,listen.
我们在一起很棒
What we have is amazing.
但我不要别人为我决定好一切
But I do not want everything decided for me!
我那样过一辈子了
I spent my whole life like that.
我跟贝瑞就是那样 那是我离开的原因之一
It's what I had with Barry. That's a reason I left.
我喜欢有未知
I like not knowing right now.
如果那样吓着了你，那很抱歉 但若你要跟我在一起就接受吧
Sorry if that scares you,but if you wanna be with me,deal with that!
好，很好 谢谢
-Okay,fine! -Thank you!
还没完呢 那我不知道
-We're not done! -I didn't know that.
跟你在一起的人 不会停止去计划他跟你的未来
You're with a guy who won't stop planning his future with you.
因为他知道我们最后会在一起
He knows we'll end up together.
如果你害怕了，很不幸 因为你必须学会接受
If that scares you,tough! You'll have to deal with that.
很好，我会的 好，因为我爱你
-I will! -Good,because I love you!
是吗？我也爱你
Oh,yeah? I love you too!
我们第一次互相说我爱你 没错
-That's the first time we've said that! -Yes,it is!
那我就要亲你了 最好是这样
-I'm gonna kiss you! -You better!
谢谢你给我的建议
Thanks for the great movie tip.
你喜欢吗？ 喜欢
-Did you like it? -Oh,yeah.
我不知道我是该在乔治毁了事业之后…
I don't know if I was happier when George Bailey destroyed the business...
…还是在唐娜哭或是在药剂师害他耳朵流血时会比较快乐
...or Donna Reed cried or when the pharmacist made his ear bleed.
好吧，我选耳朵流血 你不觉得结局很好吗？
I'll give you the ear thing,but wasn't the ending wonderful?
结局我根本就没看 我太沮丧了
I didn't watch it. I was too depressed.
剧情越来越叫人家失望 这片子应该叫：
It kept getting worse! It should've been called:
“人生真烂 就在你觉得无法更烂时，它更烂”
"It's a Sucky Life,And Just When You Think It Can't Suck Anymore,It Does!"
踢球，守住！
IKick,save! And...
…接住了
...denied!
但他抢回来，传到中间 然后准备踢，碰…
He gets it back. Pass to the middle,lines it up....
太棒了！
Yes!
那球还可以踢得更漂亮吗？
Could that shot be any prettier?
老兄，你真厉害
Man,you are incredible.
我们大学时也有这玩意儿
We had a table in college.
我不晓得 1800年也有桌上足球
Really? I didn't know they had foosball in the 1800s.
对了，你的胡子不错 青春期一到就会茂盛起来
Nice mustache. At puberty,that thing will really kick in.
我也不想太像福劳伦斯汉德森（女演员） 但晚餐做好了
Not to sound too Florence Henderson,but dinner's on the table.
再得一分
One more point.
得分
Score!
可以走了吗？
Now can we go?
看吧，所以我们才不让她玩
That's why we don't let her play.
一切都还好吧？
Is everything all right?
听我说，别跟他生气 是我们的错
Don't be mad at him. It's our fault.
我们占了他太多时间了
I'm sorry we've been hogging his time.
是呀，跟他真的是很棒
He's just really great to hang out with.
这个嘛… 不…说真的
-Well.... -No,seriously.
我跟钱德刚才还在说 他比我们的爸爸酷多了
We just talked about this. He is so much cooler than our dads.
我是说我们爸爸是还好啦 可是理查好…
Our dads are okay and all,but Richard is just
你踢我干什么？
What are you kicking me for?
我正在讲话，你…
I'm trying to talk here.
你们觉得我像父辈的？
You guys see me as a dad?
对呀 不
-Oh,yeah! -No!
你很显然不了解 我们年轻人的用语
You're just clearly not familiar with our young persons' vernacular.
我们“爸爸”的意思是指兄弟
When we say "dad," we mean "buddy."
是“伙伴”的意思
We mean "pal."
我说真的，乔伊是我爸
No,seriously. Joey's my dad.
莫妮卡也是我爸
Monica's my dad.
我们公司里还有一些我爸爸
I've even got some dads down at work.
很好
That's fine.
你们的另外一个爸爸跟我 要去有一个浪漫的夜晚了
Well,your other dad and I are gonna go have a romantic evening.
孩子们，我们改天见了
I'll just see you kids around.
晚安了
Nighty-night.
你不是一个爸
You're not a dad!
真不敢相信你干的好事
I can't believe you got us into trouble.
你还好吗？
So are you okay?
只是…
Just...
…我只是觉得自己像一百岁的样子
... I feel like I'm about a hundred.
我还以为我跟他们一样
I thought I was just one of the guys.
过来
Come here.
我会让你觉得 你跟他们一样
I'll make you feel like one of the guys.
对一个很酷的人来说 你的足球烂透了
For a really cool guy,you suck at foosball.
我痛宰了他们
I was killing them.
他们也很烂
Yeah,well they suck too.
对，然后你把有便便的尿布 丢到便便尿布桶里去
You take the poopy diaper and put it in the poopy diaper pail.
叫它们便便尿布 并不会让这个过程更可爱
Calling it a "poopy diaper" doesn't make this process any cuter.
是我们 上来吧
-It's us. -Come on up.
我去准备他其他的东西
I'll get his stuff together.
我们做得到的，是不是，班？
Okay,we can do this now,can't we,Ben?
对，我们可以
Yes,we can.
好了
There! I did it!
我换好了
I did it!
你瞧瞧
Look at that!
紧紧的包在屁屁上
It stays on and everything.
对不起，你刚刚说什么？ 你刚刚说“嗨”啊？
I'm sorry. What did you just say? Did you just say "hi"?
天啊，罗斯… 班刚说“嗨”耶
Oh,my God! Ross? Ben just said hi!
什么？ 班刚说“嗨”
-What? -Ben just said hi!
什么？那个字“嗨”吗？
What,the word "hi"?
不，是我的叔叔“嗨”
No,my Uncle Hi.
太好了，我也错过了 我错过一切了
Great! And I missed that too. I miss everything!
我猜我太有魅力了
Oh,I'm sorry. I guess I just bring it out in him.
他在哪里？ 我们想你
-Where is he? -We missed you.
我们好想你 过来，班
We missed you so much! Come here,Ben.
你们猜，班刚说了哪个字？
Guess what? Ben just said his first word.
他说什么了？
What did he say?
什么嗨不嗨的
Something about hi.
真是令人兴奋 妈咪好骄傲哦
That's so exciting! Mommy's so proud of you!
事实上比较像这样，“嗨”
You know,actually,it's more like,hi!
这可能要玩很久
This could go on for a while.
计程车还在楼下等我们呢
You're right. We've got a cab waiting.
这真好玩 好的
Well,this was fun.
我们改天一定还要这样子 班，你说怎么样呢？
We should do it again sometime,Ben. What do you say?
好吧，下一次是… 星期二
-All right,so I've got him...? -Tuesday.
再见了
Bye,you guys.
保重 再见，班
-Take care. -Bye,Ben.
他刚刚…他…他刚刚说再见吗？
Did he just say "bye"?
他说再见…
He said bye!
你说再见，他对我说再见
You said bye! He said bye to me!
没错
Yes,he did!
我已经可以幻想他去上大学了
Suddenly I'm seeing him go off to college!
我们得走了，计程车在楼下等
We've gotta go. We've got that cab downstairs.
再见…
See you later.
我看挖的这个洞好深 伯特…（《芝麻街》）
Look at this nice deep hole I dug. Hey,Bert...
…这洞是不是挖得很好？
...isn't this a nice hole here?
班，这是厄尼把伯特埋在沙里头，然后找不到他
Ben,this is the part where Ernie buries Bert in the sand and can't find him.
现在，我已经先看过了 他后来有找到他
Now,I've looked ahead on the tape,and he does find him again.
可是，在那之前呢 会先有一些让人很难受的情节
But before that happens,there's some rough going for a while.
可是我想我们挺得住
But I think we can handle it.
这些只是前面的情节 可是我知道结局会很好的…
And there's just the alphabet,but we know that ends well,so....
好，继续了
Here we go.
伯特？…
Bert? Bert?
我的朋友伯特怎么了？他刚刚还在这里
What happened to my friend Bert? He was here just a moment ago.
不，伯特不见了？
Oh,no! My old friend Bert is lost.
我真高兴你在这里
I'm so glad you're here.